Nakamura Shigeru

Sr Fullstack Engineer

Introduction

Nakamura is an ambitious professional who is always eager for new, difficult problem solving as well as solid background of software engineering and electrical engineering for the last 5 years in industry level of experience.

His experience as a senior software lead and project manager let him to have a strong background of fundamental knowledge in traditional software engineering, but also the new coming latest technologies.

He is well-respected among st industry-leading companies as a skilled developer who truly understands the client infrastructure and pain points. His dedication and detail orientation are the core traits of him. Also he has successfully worked with numerous clients to define requirements, design new system elements, implement new functionalities, and optimize existing system.

Fishing, playing basketball and drinking beer is his only hobby :) Best regards,

Nakamura Shigeru.

Education

Master of Computer Science

Tsinghua University

2013 – 2017 GPA: **86**

Portfolio

Updated Website fronted

Lxgic - https://zeft.app

This is an ecommerce platform that customers can give gift list and receiver can choose one gift of them. With this project, I contributed to update the front-end design using React, Typescript and MUI.

Excellent Design

Artezio - https://pixexid.com

Next.js free stock photos website that provides high-resolution images. The frontend was built by next.js with tailwind css.

Personal Info

bremaster0806@gmail.com

Github

Skills

React	+8 yr
Redux	+8 yr
React Hooks	+8 yr
Next.js	+5 yr
TypeScript	+5 yr
Vue.js	+6 yr
MUI	+6 yr
Tailwind CSS	+4 yr
Golang	+5 yr
Node.js	+8 yr
Express	+8 yr
HTML	+9 yr
CSS/SCSS	+9 yr
JavaScript	+9 yr
MongoDB	+5 yr
MySQL	+5 yr
Restful API	+7 yr
Cypress	+5 yr
Git	+5 yr
Jest/Enzemy	+4 yr
Vercel	+8 yr

Employment

Senior FullStack Engineer

Lxgic

Tokyo, Japan 2021 - 2024

- Updated the architecture and UI design for ecommerce platform using react.js, typescript and tailwind css.
- Refactored the frontend to modern TypeScript.
- Integrated stripe payment.
- Implement a GraphQL server with other third-party apps. Created next.js shopify app.

Tech Stacks: React, Next.js, MUI, TailwindCSS, ShopifyApp, Vue.js, Nuxt.js

Frontend Developer Developer

Artezio

Moscow, Russia 2018 - 2021

- Refactored the existing code to improve the performance of a heavy
- React front end by talking to a Node.js and Express.js via REST API.
- Improved the mobile user's experience by making applications, charts, and drawings react to touch events.
- Implement socket.io server for realtime chat system. Collaborated with the leadership.

Tech Stacks: React, Next.js, MUI, TailwindCSS, ShopifyApp, WebSocket, Node.js, Express